

A people-focused manager who is high in both organizational skills and emotional intelligence. Capable of guiding teams through complicated projects while keeping an eyeon individual employees' growth. Experienced with a variety ofschedulingand management software programs. Can create budgets and timetables, adjusting as necessary.

Professional Experience

Managerial Associate

Dallas Graphic Design, Dallas, TX July 2019 - Present

- Assemble teams of graphic artists, copywriters, and other creative professionals based on projects' needs
- Monitor performance of direct reports and conduct biannual performance reviews
- · Contact, vet, and hire contractors for specialized tasks
- · Generate project schedules and budgets
- Negotiate with vendors, resulting in an average savings of \$35,000 per project

Managerial Intern

Arkansas Technology, Little Rock, AR January 2019 - March 2019

- Scheduled meetings between team membersand project managers
- Generated budget projections to help the managerial team choose between vendors and contractors
- Created post-project briefs to update executives on projects' successes and challenges
- Reached out to contractors to request work samples and rate estimates
- Reviewed project-planning documents and gave feedback on issues such as clarity and inconsistencies

333 Third Street, Dallas, TX 33333 S,\$mith@email,com (123) 456-7890

Education

Bachelor of Human Resources Management

Dallas University, Dallas, TX Septem be r 2013 - Ju ne 2017

Master of Science in Management

Houston School Of Business, Houston, TX September 2017 - June2019

Key Skills

- Project and employee management
- Written and verbal communication
- Sch ed u I i n g a n d ru nni ng prod uctive meetings
- Conflict resolution
- Pro Workfl ow, 0 ra cl e, Scoro, a nd Smartsheet managerial software

Certifications

Certified Project Manager, HR
I nstitute of America, 2019